livecoin.net 2019-11-14

# Livecoin - Privacy policy

This Privacy Policy was last modified on January 01, 2015.

Livecoin.net ("us", "we", or "our") operates [www.livecoin.net](http://www.livecoin.net/) (the "Website"). This page informs you of our policies regarding gather, use and disclosure of our customers’ personal data received from our Website. We are not responsible for the websites hosted on any other domains. 

The only purpose we use your personal data is to maintain our Website proper functioning and improve its services for the benefit of our Customers. By using the Website, you consent to the collection and use of information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms, accessible at www.livecoin.net. 

## Information Collection And Use

While you are using our Website, we may ask you to share certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your name, e-mail address, postal address etc., ("Personal Information"). 

## Event log

Like many other sites operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Website ("Event Log"). This Event Log may contain data of your computer Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages you visited on our Website, time and date of your visit, duration of session and other statistics. 

## Cookies

Cookies are files with a small amount of data, containing an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on the hard drive of your computer.

Like many other sites, we use "cookies" to collect information. You can set your browser to reject all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you reject cookies, you may not be able to use some sections of our Website. 

## Security

Safety of your Personal Information is of top priority for us, however, please, remember, that no method of data transmission over the Internet, as well as methods of electronic storage, are 100% secure. While we are trying to use all commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its perfect security. 

## Links To Other Websites

Our Website may contain links to other websites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's website. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every website you visit. 

Livecoin.net has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party websites or services. 

## Changes To This Privacy Policy

Livecoin.net may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Website. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. 

## Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.

In 5 minutesthe system will be set into maintenance mode. All open orders handling operations will be resumed after maintenance is completed.

**Time left:**
